* #### Industries
    
* #### Solutions
    
* #### Site Navigation

* #### Additional resources

* Solutions

    * * *
    
    Resources
    
* Industries

911Cellular LLC Privacy Policy
==============================

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

By accessing this site, registering for or using any 911Cellular products or services, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. If at any time you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website or 911Cellular products and services.

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. This website will always have the most current version of the Privacy Policy available. We will alert you about any changes by updating the “Last Modified” date of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site or 911Cellular products or services following the revision of this Privacy Policy shall constitute your acceptance thereof.

### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

We collect personal information to better provide services to you. Personal Information refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify an individual. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number, or other details to help you with your experience.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register with our app or enter information on our site, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you:

* To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
    
* To improve customer service.
    
* To respond to and support your school or employer regarding its use of this site or 911Cellular products or services.

### How do we protect your information?

We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.

We do not use Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

In order to request removal of user data, contact [\[email protected\]](https://www.911cellular.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with a list of the user data you would like have to have removed.

### Do we use cookies?

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly. However, you will still be able to place orders.

### Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may also share information, including personally identifiable information, when its release is appropriate to:

* Cooperate and comply with applicable law, regulation, legal process or law enforcement or government authorities’ request.
    
* Enforce our site policies and terms of use, including investigating use or misuse of 911Cellular products or services.
    
* Protect 911Cellular or others’ rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Google

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. [https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en)

We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

### Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify you via email

* Other

Within 7 business days of being made aware of breach.

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

* Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

* Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
    
* Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
    
* Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
    
* Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
    
* Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
    
* Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at

* Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

6001 Cochran Road

Solon, OH 44139

United States

[\[email protected\]](https://www.911cellular.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Last Edited on 12-15-2023

[### _Healthcare_

Protect all of your caregivers with a multi-layered approach to safety, reducing healthcare violence and organizational liability.](https://www.911cellular.com/industries/healthcare)[### _Higher Education_

Provide your students and staff members with unprecedented safety and convenience technology while staying Clery compliant.](https://www.911cellular.com/industries/higher-education)[### _K-12 Schools_

Achieve Alyssa's Law compliance and a streamlined emergency communication workflow to your first responders and police.](https://www.911cellular.com/industries/k12schools)[### _Public Safety_

Blanket your community with efficient, smartphone-accessible tools to get in touch with the right people for any situation.](https://www.911cellular.com/industries/public-safety)

### _Healthcare_

Protect all of your caregivers with a multi-layered approach to safety, reducing healthcare violence and organizational liability.

### _Higher Education_

Provide your students and staff members with unprecedented safety and convenience technology while staying Clery compliant.

### _K-12 Schools_

Achieve Alyssa's Law compliance and a streamlined emergency communication workflow to your first responders and police.

### _Public Safety_

Blanket your community with efficient, smartphone-accessible tools to get in touch with the right people for any situation.

Stay informed on the latest in critical incident management:

[\[email protected\]](https://www.911cellular.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

© 2024 911Cellular. All rights reserved.

#### Industries

#### Solutions

#### Resources

#### About

#### Customers
